Hello everyone. My name is He, it's
spelled as h e.
That's it.
[laughter]
Yes, it is my name. It is not my
pronoun.
[laughter]
People get confused all the time. The
other day I was drinking at a pub, this
cute bloke came up to me. He was like,
"Yo, what's your name?" I said, "My name
is He."
He was like, "Huh?"
I said, "He, h e, sir." And he said,
"Nice to meet you, He."
I was like, "What? Excuse me? I am not a
hoe. You know, that's my cousin."
Yeah, she is a hoe. Yeah.
Her mom is a hoe.
And her dad is a hoe, too, you know.
[laughter]
Those hoes are loyal, though.
Yeah.
As you can tell from my outfit that I
was made in China.
Yes.
Look, guys, I'm really sorry for the
COVID.
Uh
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm sorry for it, but I didn't do
it.
I was here the whole time.
I know.
Oh, thank you. Yeah.
Yeah, last year I was roaming around the
city and this guy just yelled at me. He
was like, "Yo, go back to China."
I was like, "Sir, there's no flight."
[laughter]
Uh I left China about 3 years ago
because I feel pathetic.
Yes, [cheering] people are really
judgemental.
Uh if you're like me, over the age of
27, not dating or not married, in China,
you'll be called leftover ladies.
I know, it is brutal.
[laughter]
But I love leftovers.
Come on, who doesn't love Chinese
leftovers?
Yeah.
I know. Thank you.
We are yummy and cheap.
That is my Tinder bio. Chinese leftover,
yummy.
Just take me home and eat me.
I know.
Yes.
My parents are the one who always push
me to get married. I remember my 30th
birthday, my dad just told me. He was
like,
[sighs and gasps]
"He,
[laughter]
can you lower your standards
and get a husband?"
I was like, "What, Dad? I don't have any
standards.
You know, just like my mom."
Yep, I know.
Yeah. Yeah. I
I don't understand why people want to
get married. Almost all of my married
friends are miserable.
The other day I was chatting with a
friend, she was complaining that I wish
I hadn't married, you know. All the BS
from my in-laws, my husband is lazy, my
kid is a failure.
[laughter]
I was like, "What the heck, Mom?
Are you serious? You know?"
[applause]
No wonder I'm not married. That's my
time. Thank you guys so much.
Oh, [cheering] thank you.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[music]
OH, HELLO.
[cheering]
OH, HELLO, [screaming] TONY. KAKOU.
I THOUGHT [applause] HE WAS GOING TO
TAKE IT OFF.
I'M WEARING THE PANTS. YES. BUT
I CAN pull the naked.
Oh, no, Tony.
Okay? No, thank you. Number one,
football player naked pose.
COME ON.
[music]
HEY.
[laughter]
[cheering]
DON'T WORRY.
I'M wearing Pants. [cheering]
OKAY.
NUMBER TWO,
OKAY, horse racer naked pose.
[cheering]
Come on. COME ON.
[music]
HEY.
DON'T WORRY. I'M WEARING
PANTS.
OKAY.
NUMBER THREE,
[cheering]
JAMES BOND naked pose.
James Bond, yeah. Come on. Come on.
Hey.
[music]
[cheering]
I love it so much.
Don't worry.
I'M WEARING PANTS.
OKAY.
IT'S GENIUS.
FINALLY,
DON'T STOP. SPICE [cheering] GIRLS SPICE
GIRLS.
ONE OF THEM. ONE OF THEM. Naked pose.
COME ON. COME ON.
[music]
[cheering]
HEY.
[music]
[cheering]
DON'T WORRY. I'M WEARING PANTS.
OKAY.
[music]
THAT'S THE BEST THING I'VE SEEN IN AGES.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
[music]
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
[music]
OH, TONY. Good way.
Okay, okay. Tony, you might actually be
my favorite contestant of the whole
series so far. THANK YOU.
ARIGATO GOZAIMASU. NO, ARIGATO gozaimasu
to you. YEAH, THANK YOU.
OH MY GOD.
COME ON,
TONY. BRUNO, WHAT DID YOU THINK?
I HAVE TO SAY YOU DEFINITELY HAVE BALLS.
GREAT. WHAT CAN I SAY?
[cheering]
AMANDA, TONY, you are absolutely unique
and it felt very Britain's Got Talent. I
loved it. Thank you.
Simon. Honestly, you are the funniest
contestant we've had on all year.
Seriously.
Funny [cheering] boy.
Really, really funny and original.
Thank you. Simon naked pose. No, no, no,
no, no.
Simon. No.
[cheering]
Always keep them waiting, Tony.
We're all going to have to take a vote
now, though.
Oh, it's a yes from me. Yes. [cheering]
Amanda.
It's a yes from me, Tony. Thank you.
[cheering]
Tony Kakou. Tony Kakou. IT'S A YES FROM
ME. ME?
YES. [cheering]
SIMON. TONY, HONESTLY, YOU are
unbelievable. Unbelievable?
You You are brilliant. Simon Simon love
me. I absolutely love you. Unbelievable.
You have four yeses. Yes.
[cheering]
[music]
Yes. Thank you, guys. [music]
Thank you very much.
[cheering]
Nice to meet you, Victor.
[laughter]
Hello, Mom.
Hi.
Hello.
Sorry, a bit nervous. [laughter]
Who are you? Uh I'm Phil W. Green. Um
I'm 21 and I'm going to be doing comedy
impressions. YAY.
[laughter]
PHIL, DO YOU DO THIS FULL TIME? UH NO, I
DON'T, NO.
What do you do? I work at Body Shop at
the moment as a customer consultant.
I bet your dream is to be a big
international star.
love to be on stage.
[music]
I'm Philip Green. I'm 21 and I'm a
customer consultant at Body Shop, but
it's not what I want to do forever.
Have you done anything like this before,
Phil? Not this, no. Never done anything
like this before, no.
I'm going to go out there and just have
a laugh. As soon as I'm out there,
that's it. Can't come off.
You'll be fine. I have never performed
this talent in in of anyone apart from
my friends. I am so nervous to go on
that stage in front of all those judges
and all those people cuz I don't know
what they're going to think. Are they
going to buzz me? I don't
I like to think I've got what it takes
to win.
I like to think
I like to think that I've got what it
takes to win Britain's Got Talent.
Philip, did you bring anyone with you?
Uh yeah, my friend Christie.
Does she work at Body Shop? She did, but
she's recently left.
Why?
Because she found a better job.
[laughter]
FOUND A BETTER JOB. SORRY.
WHERE? Um she now works um at Barrett's.
So
[laughter]
shoes.
HOW OLD IS GOOD AFTER ALL OF THIS?
OKAY, WELL LOOK, PHILIP, you've got
roughly 2 minutes. Let's do it.
Okay.
[applause]
Hello. I'm let me introduce you today.
And today
we're going to be health working out. So
everyone put your hands out in front of
you, spread your legs, AND DO SOME
SQUATS. [laughter]
LIE ON THE BABY ON MARTIN Fowler's sofa.
Isn't that right? DOT COTTON WOULD BE
PROUD, WOULDN'T SHE?
OOH. It's so nice to be here on my wee
show. And today's guest is absolutely
fantastic. You know what? I'm going to
meet her. Hello.
Thanks for having me on your show,
Lorraine. I'm so nervous.
And then
Oh my god. I mean, I saw those ones and
And then I saw even more ones.
And then I tried my new ones.
And I was being sick everywhere.
Oh my goodness, have you seen the
interior in here? It is awful. Isn't
that right, Kim?
Oh, my love.
Oh, that stinks.
Dance. It's me, Louis Spence. DANCE,
EMILY AND DUNCAN.
COME ON, DUNCAN. EMILY. COME ON, DUNCAN.
EMILY. DUNCAN. DUNCAN. And down. Duncan.
And down. AND SPENCE.
DUNCAN.
OH.
OOH.
[cheering]
[music]
I LIKE HIM. I LIKE HIM A LOT.
[cheering and music]
[applause]
THE BRILLIANT THING ABOUT YOUR ACT WAS
THAT YOU WERE JUST laughing before you
even did anything. Thanks, AMANDA.
[laughter]
DAVID.
YOU'RE LIKE A BUTCH version of me.
You're very, very funny guy.
I'd like to see some more of you in the
act as well. Cuz you are hysterically
funny as you as well.
Are you sure you're not related to
Stacey Solomon? I WISH I WAS.
[laughter]
I'VE SEEN HER FROM A DISTANCE and I was
like, "Stacey." But no.
I think you're really funny, lovable. Do
you need a wee? No, no, no. I'm just
really nervous. Sorry.
Simon.
It was like the world record for how
many [music] impersonations you can do
in 2 minutes. I found it difficult to
keep up with some of them. The ones that
were were great.
Oh, thanks, Simon.
But you are a naturally funny guy.
Oh, thanks.
Slightly bonkers.
[cheering]
But I like that.
You're going to take a boat.
David, [music] yes or no?
I'm going to say yes.
Please.
[music]
It's a yes from me.
Simon.
Uh and we have actually had some good
impressionists on the show this year.
Uh so you have got some competition.
But I am going to say
yes.
THAT'S FOUR YESES. YOU'RE THROUGH TO THE
NEXT ROUND.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
IT'S NICE MEETING YOU ALL.
BYE-BYE.
[music]
OH MY GOD.
Oh my gosh. Well done.
Well done. You did it.
You did it. You did it. Funny guy. He is
very funny.
be quite fun to have two impressionists
[music] in the final. And an impression
off. So your first time out on stage
doing this, how did it feel?
I'm so glad they laughed.
[laughter]
That's all I can say, like that. Good.
Well, we'll see you again. You [music]
got four yeses. Well done. Well done.
Thank you very much. Cheers. Enjoy. Go
and celebrate.
See you next time.
[cheering]
Oh, little Ned.
[applause]
IS THAT YOU, DEC?
[laughter]
PLEASE, SIR, TELL US YOUR NAME. UH I'm
Ned. How old are you, Ned? I'm 8. So
cute.
Where are YOU [clears throat] FROM?
MAIDSTONE.
[cheering]
WHO'S HERE with you today? Well, I'm
with my mom,
my dad, my stepmom, my sister, my other
sister, and my brother.
Fantastic. Do you perform for friends
and family? Do you get up in school and
do shows? Yeah. The stage is yours, sir.
Good luck.
[applause]
I love him already.
Go on, Ned.
Why were people so excited about that
talking dog on Britain's Got Talent?
Amanda Holden's been on it for years.
[cheering]
[screaming]
Savage.
It was really fun meeting Ant and Dec
backstage, but I'm never quite sure
which one's supposed to be THE FUNNY
ONE.
[laughter]
OH, HE'S KILLING US ALL.
ALICIA. OH, NO.
Alicia laughing. Oh, no.
Alicia not dancing.
[applause]
That was good.
Simon.
Go on, son. He reminds me a lot of my
dad.
He's a cross-dresser. He gets especially
cross when he can't FIND HIS SOCKS.
[laughter]
I WAS REALLY WORRIED FOR David Walliams
when he swam in the River Thames for
charity because of all that garbage
going in his mouth.
But since I've been watching BGT, I'm
relieved it's all coming out again.
[cheering]
Very good. WELL DONE, NED.
NED, I LOVED THE WAY THAT you took the
mickey out of us. It was really quite
savage.
[laughter]
I'm Axel Blake and I'm from West London.
So Axel, what made you sign up for BGT
this year?
Well, I've got 12-year-old son who's in
the audience. Nice.
Yeah.
So I just wanted them to believe in
yourself, you know? Put your mind to it
and you can make it happen.
[applause]
And do you have a day job? Uh yes, I do
um property maintenance. If you need a
kitchen done, Simon, let me know. I do
actually. It's all Give me a call.
I will. Good. I want a good rate. No,
no, no.
[laughter]
Come. We're friends now. Yeah, okay,
cool. Press that and we're cool, yeah?
[laughter]
I'm really curious with you cuz you got
you got your day job. This is obviously
what you want to do. Has there ever been
a moment where you've almost lost your
confidence and thought, "I'm not going
to do this"?
100%. 100% there's been that time, but
when you have family that's looking at
you and inspired by you, that's what
keeps you going. Yeah. So my son and my
daughter, that's what's that's the
reason. That's the reason.
[cheering]
[applause]
All right. Well, we wish you the best of
luck.
Go for it.
[applause]
How we doing, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN? MAKE
SOME NOISE.
I WAS GOING TO DRIVE HERE TODAY. I
REALIZED I DON'T HAVE A LICENSE, so
Don't worry, I drove anyways. I drove
anyways.
I took the tube. I took the tube. I've
got a love-hate relationship with the
tube. You know? I love when it's empty.
I hate when it's packed. Can't stand it.
Fight people up for the armrest. Have
you ever done that?
I know you don't.
This old lady is strong. Oh my.
[laughter]
Have it. Have it, Margaret. Have it.
JUST HAVE IT.
[laughter]
SOME PEOPLE DO THEIR MAKEUP ON THE TUBE
AS WELL. MAKE some noise if you ever
done your makeup ON THE TUBE.
LEGEND.
COUPLE WEEKS ago I saw a woman she was
doing her whole makeup. Few stops later
she was a whole new person.
I was so impressed. I STARTED CLAPPING.
I WAS LIKE, "YOU KNOW WHAT? YEAH. You
know, she looked down on me like
You may be a nine out of 10 now, but you
was a minus two at King's Cross last
year.
[laughter]
I walked off the train like this,
inspired. Yeah.
On a brighter note, just recently my
fiance gave birth to little baby girl.
Don't clap, Simon. Don't clap. I didn't
say the baby's mine, did I?
[laughter]
I'm joking. She's mine.
Pandemic baby as well, you know. Yeah.
So, we had to give her a fitting name.
So, we named her Pfizer. Yeah.
Technology is moving at such a crazy
speed, evolving crazy. You got the
metaverse, you know, you got
cryptocurrency.
I still get excited about my contactless
card when I use it.
I do. WHEN I USE IT
I LOVE THE NOISE.
I'VE GOT A JACKET WITH A POCKET ON HIS
ARM. Sometimes I'll leave my card in the
arm and I'll pay with my arm.
Just to confuse the cashier.
That'll be 19 pounds 30.
Next week I'm going back. I'm going to
leave my card in my back pocket. That'll
be 22 pounds 60.
Then I walk off
in style.
Who's in a happy relationship? MAKE SOME
NOISE.
YEAH, ME AND MY FIANCE HAVE BEEN
together for years, years, years, years.
And my friends ask me, "How do you do
it? How you been together for so long?"
Through the pandemic, baby. And I just
say, "Find you a woman that, you know,
loves you, understands your flaws, and
find you a woman that has a good sense
of humor."
Just make sure those three women don't
find OUT ABOUT AISHA.
YEAH, BUT WE DON'T REALLY have issue. In
fact, I'm like, "The biggest issue we
have is I hate when she would imitate my
voice in argument and it sounds nothing
like my voice." I can't stand it. I hate
it. She'll come up to me, "I asked you
what time you're coming home and you
said to me, 'I don't know what time I'M
COMING HOME.'"
[laughter]
I DON'T SOUND LIKE THAT.
WHAT I DO NOW, I've got a way to get her
back. I imitate her voice back and guess
what? She don't like it.
So, I did tell you what time I was
coming home and you said, "Well, make
sure you come back at A DECENT TIME."
[laughter]
I DON'T SOUND LIKE THAT. YES, YOU DO.
SHE GETS ANGRY. "GET OUT OF MY FACE. GET
OUT OF MY FACE." I SAID, "ALL RIGHT,
I'LL GET OUT OF YOUR FACE, BUT HOW DO I
DO IT?"
In style.
My name's Axel Blake. THANK YOU.
[cheering]
[music]
[applause]
WELL DONE, AXEL. DAVID, WHAT DID you
think? A comedy superstar is born
tonight on that stage.
So funny. You made it all seem so
effortless. You got a wonderful, so
likable personality. And everything you
said was brilliantly funny and original.
I loved it, Axel. Thank you.
Well done, Axel.
Super, super, super confident. First
person, honestly, who's ever made a joke
about COVID and was funny.
I I know it's a bit of a cliche, but,
you know, after what everybody's gone
through over the last couple of years,
boy, A, did we needed this show back on
air. We needed acts like you. There's
one thing I have to tell you, though.
I kind of like a granite top.
I like a waste disposal unit.
I want 25% off and you get this.
[music and cheering]
[cheering and music]
[screaming]
[cheering]
[music]
We needed you.
[cheering]
Absolutely brilliant.
[music]
[cheering]
[applause]
[cheering and music]
I love this man already.
I mean, hello, hello. You haven't done
anything already. THE CROWD [cheering]
IS going crazy for you. I paid them all
to do that. So, that was I got you.
Venmo. Okay.
What is your name? Uh my name is Jordan
Conley. How old are you? I'm 29. And
where do you come from? I'm from Garden
Grove, California. And you came here to
dance? No, I actually came here to do
stand-up comedy.
[cheering]
[applause]
Jordan, how long have you been a
comedian?
I've been doing it for seven years now.
Okay. And that's how you make a living?
I I would I would like to say yes, but
also, do you want your fries with more
ketchup? You know what I mean? Like,
does that make sense? Okay. I just want
to confirm.
[laughter]
That's So, yeah. But that didn't
discourage you because here you are.
Oh, yeah.
[cheering]
So, what is your dream? What Where do
you see yourself in the future? I have
very, very big dreams. So, my dream
right now is all based off of Kevin
Hart. Kevin Hart did a football stadium.
I think it was like 73,000 people. My
goal is 73,001.
[cheering]
[applause]
That's ambition. Okay. So, let's see
what you've got. Okay. Thank you.
[cheering]
[applause]
So, I come from a very tough upbringing.
Like, I have a military family. My
parents met in the Marine Corps. Like,
that's where my parents met, right?
[cheering]
Like, my dad came to me. He was like,
"Yo, it'd be so cool if my oldest son
could join the military." I was like,
"Dad, it'd be so cool if you adopted
somebody older than me." You
[laughter]
I'm not that guy. I feel like if you're
going to go overseas, you need to be
willing to take secrets to the grave.
I'm not that guy, okay? You know what
I'm saying? Like
Like, if I go overseas, let's say I get
captured. I become a prisoner of war.
I'm telling my secrets, your secrets,
and Victoria's Secrets. You know what
I'm saying?
[cheering]
I'm telling them all.
Like, I could be in a hostage situation
and this guy is trying to threaten me.
He's like, "What's it going to take to
get the secrets from you?" I'm like,
"Sir, a pen and paper. Just
Get Get Listen, give me that. Put the
knives away. This is a celebration. You
caught the right guy, okay?
[applause]
The toughest person in my family is by
far my mom. She's tough. She's old
school. Like, if you ever got in trouble
with her, she would turn whatever
situation with you into a horror movie
scene. I promise you.
There's one day She says, "Jordan, did I
tell you to come downstairs to do these
dishes? YOU BETTER DO THESE dishes
before you get in trouble." I lost in a
video game. I got angry. I snapped. I
said, "You ain't done nothing all day. I
suggest you stay downstairs and do them
dishes before you get in trouble."
Out of nowhere, this is all I heard.
"Who the hell you think you're talking
to?"
As soon as I heard that voice, all the
power in my house cut off, okay? The
lights cut off. These crows came out of
my closet. My windows opened up. There
was these two little girls in a school
uniform jumping rope and singing. They
were like, "One, two, your mama's coming
for YOU." I
[laughter]
I WOKE UP A WEEK LATER CONFUSED.
[cheering]
THANK YOU, GUYS.
[music]
[music and cheering]
[cheering]
[music]
I thought it was spectacular. There's
something about your energy. I think
[music] you have the all the future
ahead of you. Thank [cheering] you so
much.
You are just naturally funny because you
are super, super talented. Absolutely.
[cheering and music]
[applause]
When you did the voice, you really
cracked me up.
This was a really really really good
audition. I like you a lot.
[music]
I mean, you are so fast. It's crazy how
you go from here to there and here to
there, but like I was like following.
And then we're in your house and I was
there with you and it was all funny and
I'm doing the same thing to my kids when
they don't behave. Guess what?
You know, there are certain people you
mentioned Kevin Hart and one of the
things that makes these people stars is
there are people that come out and then
they do an act and then there are people
that come out you believe there's no
separation between who [music] that
person is and this is not an act. The
difference [cheering] is people go I
love Kevin Hart. People are going to say
I love Jordan Conley. It's not his act.
I love him.
[cheering]
[music]
[applause]
So, we're going to give YOU A VOTE.
[cheering]
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU
YOUR FIRST
YES.
YOUR SECOND YES.
[cheering]
I'M GOING to give you A THIRD YES.
I'M GOING TO GIVE you roughly 4,000
yeses.
[cheering]
[music]
I've never seen you laugh so much. You
were just so funny. But you were really
like you were doing LIKE THIS THING.
[laughter]
OH, JORDAN. HEY, BABY, give me a hug.
GIVE ME A
YOU look emotional. I mean, a bee fell
in my eye during the performance. One
more time.
[music]
Was that it?
[cheering]
Is that it?
[laughter]
I thought he was going to do stand-up
comedy. [cheering]
[cheering]
[music]
Simon's face is like this.
Look at Simon's face.
In Norway that means YOU'RE DOING REALLY
GOOD.
[music]
OH.
[cheering]
Is there any more? Is there any more?
Come on, please.
[music]
[cheering]
Honestly.
[music]
[cheering]
Uh-oh. Don't do this to me.
[music]
Yes.
[cheering]
[music]
Right. Okay. Any more?
[cheering]
You want more? No.
No.
[music]
I LOVE THIS ACT SO MUCH.
[applause and cheering]
[music]
Celebrating
[cheering]
[cheering and applause]
Good evening. Good evening. What's your
name? I'm Micky. Micky? Yeah.
Where you from, darling? I'm from the
beautiful city of Leeds.
[cheering]
How old are you, Micky? Uh I'm 36. Do
you have a day job or is this your
full-time job?
I am a part-time primary school teacher.
Oh, lovely.
Lovely.
[cheering]
Are you enjoying your food?
[laughter]
[cheering]
Yeah, you've got to wait, you know.
The stage is yours, Micky. Go for it.
Thank you very much. Cheers.
This is called the absolutely amazing
song. Yes.
About traveling round Europe. Oh. That
rhymes.
[cheering]
I like him. I'm off to Paris
in a Yaris.
This next song
I know this is supposed to be a comedy
routine, but I've I've suffered loss
recently. Aw.
So, I just want to get this off my
chest. I am
Joe, I'll I'll play this song cuz I I
get a bit emotional talking about it.
I can't believe I've lost you.
I can't believe you've gone.
I need you to know that
you did nothing wrong.
First time I saw you
just hang in there.
The checkout lady said, "Do you want to
buy one of these?"
And I said,
"All right, go on then, yeah."
You were my bag for life.
He's what? Bag for life.
What? My bag for life.
You really go to the supermarket
and you can either buy a cheap carrier
bag or a bag for life, which is better
quality and a bit more expensive.
You cost almost 10 p and I only used you
twice.
[music]
The other bags I use compared to you are
slack.
I always feel that the handle strap is
going to
Does that happen to you a LOT AS WELL?
[laughter]
BAG FOR LIFE.
[cheering and music]
MUSIC, START.
[cheering]
[applause]
WHAT?
[bell]
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO. OH, NO, NO, NO, NO.
This is me after [cheering] being wait
FOR GUYS ALL MY LIFE.
It's my birthday. Can you sing birthday
song?
[music]
What's going on right now?
People use up birthday candles with a
fork holding them through.
[music]
[cheering]
One more. One more.
Oh, he's [cheering] gorgeous.
Oh, I could take more.
Last super human.
[music]
What? He's going to burst the balloon.
What was that? [music] It's the dawn, I
think.
OH, NO.
[music]
HEY MATE.
Get him off. Go get Go get get.
LET'S GO.
I'M FALLING.
GO.
[cheering]
COME ON.
[music]
Come on.
This is it.
[music]
OH, NO.
OH, I JUST
just wanted to do it now.
[applause]
[cheering]
Come on, again. Let's go. LET'S GO.
AGAIN, AGAIN, AGAIN, AGAIN.
ONE MORE?
WE'VE GOT TO GET THIS [cheering] TO
WORK.
[cheering]
Can I help?
Yeah.
Let's get this a bit closer.
Come on, let's go.
[music]
Come on.
I consider it a challenge before all the
[music and screaming]
[cheering]
Yes,
AT LAST.
[music]
[cheering]
[applause]
YES.
[music]
WE DID IT.
[cheering]
[music]
ITCHI KAWA, CONGRATULATIONS. Thank you.
There's no other place for you really
than this show.
I can assure you one thing, it's not
fake, it's real.
[laughter]
I am literally speechless. It's like an
out-of-body experience.
Listen, one series on this show, that
will become normal.
Oh my god.
I can't believe that I enjoyed that. I
actually really enjoyed it.
[applause]
[music]
What I'm most looking forward to is
potentially saying, "Your Royal Highness
King Charles, may we proudly present the
winner of Britain's Got Talent."
We're going to take a vote, Itchi Kawa.
It's a yes from me. Thank you.
Alesha, I enjoyed that, but I don't know
if I want to see it again though. What?
[cheering]
You want to see it again?
Okay, but the potential is a yes. Thank
you.
[laughter]
[cheering]
Bruno.
Oh, it's a no for me. I
[laughter]
Oh, we have a buddy, it's a no. I mean
[cheering]
Here we go.
Simon. Well, I didn't know what was
going on.
I genuinely hadn't got a clue.
And then I understood.
I remember watching Rocky for the first
time thinking
[music]
one of the most suspenseful, exciting
end of a movie I've ever seen.
And that was up there.
I've never wanted a balloon to burst so
much in my life.
Take [music] that buzzer away.
I'm thrilled [music] to give you your
30th.
Thank you.
[cheering]
[music]
It is good to see you guys out, man. I
was talking to the producers, they're
like, "Hey Emo, we're very excited to
have you on the show. Um we just have a
question, have you booked your
accommodation yet?" I said, "No, I
haven't. I'm just looking for somewhere
close by, cultured." As soon as I said
cultured, they said, "We got the perfect
place."
When you said Blacktown.
Is that actually a town here? It is a
town.
I was like, "Ooh, that sounds nice."
Soon as I got there, I was like, "Ooh,
this ain't nice."
[laughter]
So I moved areas. I thought this area
was nice. It was called Penrith. Have
you heard of this?
[cheering]
Yeah, uh it's rough. Uh
But it is a massive upgrade from
Blacktown though, cuz I went from living
around poor black people to now living
around poor white people.
[laughter]
And I love it.
Every now and then I get I've been
getting like a random white guy come up
and ask me for like loose change.
And I give it to them.
But I do it for the wrong reasons
though, ladies and gentlemen. I do it
because I kind of feel like I'm
rewriting history.
[laughter]
Every time I give them change, I'm like,
"Here you go, my man. Just don't spend
it all on drugs."
[laughter]
If only my mom could see me now.
Oh, she's not dead. She's not here.
I spoke to her on FaceTime this morning.
She's like, "Hey, how's uh Penrith
going?" I'm like, "Ma, it's so
beautiful, very multicultural. You
should see it. The white people ask me
for money."
And she was so proud. She's like, "Oh my
god, you're doing very well, my son."
And then she calls my father into the
FaceTime. She's like, "Michael,
come and have a look at your son.
He has become the king of the whites."
[laughter]
I'm going to get a buzz off soon.
Uh how does this work?
So, I just want to make
Oh, my mouth is so dry.
Here we go. Here we go.
Uh
how unprofessional. I'm so sorry.
What is very hard for for black people
to find
[applause]
There's been a lot of tension between
white and black people over the last
couple of years. But I think it's
because we don't understand each other
because of our differences in culture.
And for us to ever move forward, I feel
like we all have to do our part. Um
would you agree?
Yes.
[cheering]
Yes, I think white people, you need to
stop assuming that all black people are
out to steal things that are not theirs.
And uh black people,
man, we need to stop trying to steal
back our stuff from white people, man.
I think it's important if we're ever
going to make a change, we have to start
educating the younger generation. Like
for example, white people, you need to
stop lying to your kids. This is my
personal favorite lie. Make sure you
finish off all your dinner because
somewhere in Africa
[laughter]
there's a child that would love to eat
it.
Nonsense.
What you guys don't realize is African
parents tell their kids a similar thing.
Like I remember my mom used to tell me,
"Son, make sure you finish off all your
dinner because somewhere in Australia
there's a child eating food without
seasoning, son."
This is sick. Australia's Got Talent.
Who would have thought as a kid that
survived two refugee camps would be on
TV? Ladies and gentlemen, I've been Emo
Majok. Thank you. YEAH.
[cheering]
[music]
[applause]
OH, VERY, VERY GOOD.
[cheering]
[screaming]
[music]
[cheering]
[music and cheering]
OH MY GOD, that's amazing.
That was fantastic. you very much.
Fantastic. This is yours.
Where you from? Um I'm from South
Norfolk. What's your day job, Ben? Uh I
I do this act. Okay, I'm not going to
ask what it is cuz we like surprises. Uh
tell me why you've entered the show this
year. Well, my my two little boys, they
say, "Come on, Daddy, you've got to be
on Britain's Got Talent."
So, you got sons, you got kids?
two children. Okay, anything else?
Yeah, uh well, they did have a cat.
Yeah.
[laughter]
Yeah, I won't go there. All right, Ben,
good luck. Thank you ever so much.
[cheering]
[applause]
Well, you see, I think my little stint
now is all about uh me uh mishearing
lyrics in music, see? I mean, it all
started when I went to see The Lion
King. ANYBODY SEE THE LION KING?
OH, I LOVE THE LION KING, BUT I MUST
HAVE MISHEARD SOMETHING, RIGHT? Because
I thought the first song WAS ABOUT THE
ARSENAL CLUB FOOTBALL MANAGER.
That's funny.
What I did then, right? Had a little
think to myself, "Oh,
maybe there's other songs, right? That
you can hear that you think maybe
they're singing something different,
right?" So, I've amalgamated loads, and
it's just for you. Hit it, SHIRLEY.
OH, YEAH.
[laughter]
[music]
[singing]
[laughter]
[music]
AMANDA.
[cheering]
[applause]
[music]
[singing]
THANKS FOR LISTENING.
[cheering]
[music]
[applause]
Very good.
Brilliant.
Good evening.
Hello.
What is your name?
My name is Aiko, and I am from Japan.
[cheering]
I live here now, and uh daytime I'm a
translator, and I love my job because
when I screw up, I'm the only person who
KNOWS ABOUT IT.
SO, TODAY YOU'RE COMING TO AGT to do
what? I here to do A STAND-UP COMEDY.
[cheering]
YOU WANT TO START ALREADY?
Sounds good to me.
Okay.
[applause]
My name is Aiko.
In Japanese In Japanese it means love
child. So, I looked up the dictionary.
It says illegitimate child.
My last name is Tanaka. It means in the
rice field.
So, my whole name is illegitimate child
in the rice field.
[laughter]
Nice to meet you.
[cheering]
[applause]
I love rice.
[laughter]
Me, too.
Is this a rice crowd?
[cheering]
I just got THE CITIZENSHIP. YEAH.
[applause]
UNTIL I GOT MY CITIZENSHIP, I never had
a road rage.
If somebody cut me off, I'd be like,
"Oh, so sorry. I was driving too slow."
[laughter]
But the day I got the citizenship,
somebody cut me off, I'm like, "What the
heck? You can't cut me off. This is my
land."
[cheering]
[applause]
That's when I realized I become true
American.
[cheering]
That was great. You're hilarious.
Because I felt entitled.
[cheering]
OH.
[applause]
Before the citizenship, somebody hold
the door for me, I ran really fast. I'm
like, "Thank you so much."
After the citizenship, I'm like, "You
hold the door, you peasant."
I got sassy.
I love [cheering] her.
[applause]
Racist people always say, "Immigrants
should not be working."
I agree.
[applause]
We work too much.
[cheering]
[applause]
Now, whenever I feel lazy and I take a
nap, I'm like, "I'm doing this for
America."
[cheering]
Thank you. That's my time.
[music]
[cheering]
It was so funny. Thank you. I mean, I
was really enjoying it, and I think all
of us were enjoying it. I mean, THANK
YOU.
JOB. [cheering]
WHY ARE YOU SO EMOTIONAL?
[laughter]
I struggle with
insecurity. A lot of people say I cannot
do it cuz this is not my language, but
then I had one person who really
believed in me, which is my mom. YOUR
MOM.
[cheering]
[applause]
LAST YEAR DURING PANDEMIC, SHE passed
away.
Aw. She wanted me to go for my dream.
[cheering]
[applause]
I love her. How long have you been doing
this?
For few years. I perform everywhere. I
perform in the prison. It's
Well, it's important to have a captive
audience, and you found one.
I think your career is about to
skyrocket, young lady.
[cheering]
Mama was right. Heidi.
From jail to America's Got Talent.
I also thought you were hilarious. Thank
you. But since you have your
citizenship, don't Don't Don't get into
trouble.
Don't get into trouble. That's going to
be your bread and butter, I'm telling
you. But uh I had a lot of fun.
[cheering]
Simon, what did you think? I mean, so
funny, so naughty.
[cheering]
From the minute you walked out,
you got us. You know, and the best sign
of a comedian's doing well, obviously,
[music] is the audience.
[cheering]
And I really liked your reaction
afterwards, cuz I could see how much
this reaction meant to you as well. So,
I would like to give you your first yes.
[cheering and screaming]
[music]
I'm going to give you YOUR SECOND YES.
[cheering]
[screaming]
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU YOUR THIRD YES.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU GOT FOUR.
[cheering and screaming]
[music]
[cheering]
WAS SHE NOT BRILLIANT, THOUGH?
HILARIOUS.
AMAZING. AMAZING.
[applause]
[music]
HELLO.
You look quite scary.
[music]
Okay, so so So, what is your name,
please? I'm Lioz. Where are you from
originally? Israel.
What is it that you're doing today? I'm
a mentalist. You're a mentalist. I can
read people's minds.
[music]
My power is mind reading,
telepathy, and I can see the future.
[music]
I don't do magic. I'm the only one in
the world with these abilities. The
British audience are going to see
something that they never seen before.
They're going to be amazed.
Good luck. Thank you.
I've seen this guy before in America.
[applause]
Good evening. Good evening.
What are you not doing?
Good evening. Only you.
Did you not do it? I did it. Yes, you
did it. Huh?
Why you said it?
Good evening. Good evening.
Thank you.
Sorry.
I need a volunteer.
You.
Come up on stage.
[music]
What's your name? Amanda. Amanda? Yes.
Tell the truth.
Is that you?
Yes.
[applause]
Here I have two boxes. I want you to
choose one of the boxes.
Now,
turn around, back to back.
I want you to open the box. Inside, you
will find plastic bags with different
colors. I want you to think at one of
the colors and take it out. Now, put the
box on the floor.
Open the plastic bag with two ends and
think on the color.
Now, I want you to count to 10
slowly and both of us will turn to the
audience at the same time. Start
counting.
1 2
5 6 7 Oh, wait. Start from the
beginning.
1 2
Slowly.
2 Yeah, now it's good.
3 4 5 6 7 8 9
[laughter]
[applause]
Thank you.
It's a souvenir. Thank you. But wait,
wait, wait.
Oh, oh. No, I took something from you.
You didn't even notice. Check good, what
did I take from you? What?
I took something from you.
You're missing something.
HERE IS YOUR WALLET.
THANK YOU.
WHAT? OH, IT'S GOOD. AND YOU.
I took something from you, too. Good,
what did I take from you? I don't know.
HERE IS YOUR WALLET.
AND YOU.
THANK YOU.
NO, YOUR WALLET.
[laughter]
WHAT'S INSIDE? YOUR WALLET.
[cheering]
THANK YOU.
[applause]
[cheering]
OH, HE'S STOLEN IT.
[music]
[applause]
[cheering]
MY HEAD HURTS FROM LAUGHING.
DAVID, WHAT DID YOU THINK? WELL, I think
you're a absolute comedy genius. It was
brilliant.
It's not comedy.
Well, then I think you're screwed cuz
you're the world's worst mentalist.
It was genius. It was just brilliant.
You had us in the palm of your hands and
you have an incredible presence about
you. And it was hilariously funny.
Well, it's magic.
I think the act is very, very funny and
I would love to see you go a long way.
I now understand that this guy is a
genius.
So, I have to start this with a yes.
Thank you.
[cheering and music]
It's a yes for me.
[cheering]
Four yeses.
Thank you all.
I love you, Britain.
[cheering]
Thank you.
[applause]
Amazing. Thank you. I love it.
Funny.
Brilliant.
[applause]
Hi.
Who are you? Where are you from? Uh my
name is Jack Williams. I am from
Indianapolis, Indiana.
And I am guessing you are a magician.
Close. I am A VENTRILOQUIST.
DO YOU ALSO KNOW WHO'S A very good
ventriloquist? Right there. Fellow
ventriloquist. Yeah.
We actually had three winners so far.
Exactly. It's honestly big shoes to
fill. Terry was one of the first
ventriloquist I ever saw and when I saw
him on the stage, I just thought like I
just want to do that. That's amazing.
That's why I wanted to come here today.
I want to do this live like on the Vegas
strip.
Well, [cheering]
good luck to you and we can't wait to
MEET YOUR FRIEND.
[applause]
GUYS, GIVE IT UP FOR MY GOOD buddy
Foster. Ready, buddy? Yeah.
HERE WE GO.
HELLO.
HERE WE ARE, BUDDY. AGT. My plan is
working.
[cheering]
[applause]
What's your plan? Well, basically I used
you to smuggle me out here and now I'm
going to show my talent.
[cheering]
He's funny.
He is
so good. What's your talent?
Ventriloquism.
That's what I'm doing right now. Really?
Yes.
You think you're a better ventriloquist
than me? You think you could talk
without moving your lips? Well, I don't
have any, so yeah. Okay.
[laughter]
Let's see who's the better ventriloquist
by doing some tongue twisters. I'll
start by saying Sally sells seashells by
the seashore and then you go after.
Okay, okay.
Sally sells sea
Sally Come on. Okay.
Sally It's like this. Sally sells
seashells by the seashore. Sally sells
seashells by the seashore.
[cheering]
[applause]
Can you do that without moving your
mouth?
No. No, I can't.
I love him. I'm going to do something I
said I would never do. You wouldn't.
I would.
Please.
No.
I'm going to throw your voice. What?
[snorts]
[laughter]
Wow.
I threw your voice. It's gone.
It's gone. It's over there.
[cheering]
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Listen, listen.
I I I I think I hear it coming back.
[laughter]
I
I have your voice.
A-
And that means
I have your voice.
[applause]
Simon. Yes.
Help me.
Here, here. Come here. COME HERE.
[groaning and screaming]
THAT'S BETTER.
YOU'RE GIVING IT UP FOR FOSTER,
EVERYBODY.
[cheering]
WOW, [cheering] THE JUDGES ARE ON THEIR
FEET.
IT WAS A FAIRY TALE of love. Thank you.
This is the story about [music] love
when a guy meets a girl in a bar.
He sees the girl.
He looks at her.
And all he wants to say is a great big
Hello.
Is it me [music] you're looking for?
She looked lovely.
The dress that night she was wearing was
gold.
She wasn't looking at him,
[music]
so he showed her his best dance moves.
What the
say?
[music]
What the
say?
As he's doing shuffling.
[cheering]
She comes over. She says to the guy,
"Hey, I'm a little thirsty. You want a
drink? What you want?" Tequila. What?
Tequila. Why? It makes me happy. Fair
enough.
The girl looks at the guy and says, "I'm
sorry. I've got to go to the toilet."
[music]
"Don't go," he says. "Please don't go."
Please don't go.
I love this act.
[music and singing]
[cheering]
Suddenly,
the girl comes back. I'm so excited.
I just can't
[music]
The girl laughs at the guy and says,
"Hey, want to come back to my place for
coffee?"
The guy says, "Hey,
[music]
[cheering]
So, the guy got with the girl
and now
they've been together for 45 years.
And that
is the fairy tale of love. Thank you for
watching. [cheering] Hello. Hello,
darling. Hello. Hello, what's your name?
Um my name is Robert. Um how old are
you, Robert? Um I I I just turned 30 11
years ago.
So,
[laughter]
Is this your job or do you have a normal
job?
Um I teach tiny little primary school
children music as well. So, I do that,
which is nice.
Okay, best of luck.
[cheering]
[applause]
Right, so um ba- basically I've I've
written a song specifically for for you,
which makes me nervous and and and also
I'm slightly nervous cuz I've got
something called dyslexia, which is
which was very good for music cuz when I
was young I taught myself the piano,
although it's not so good as I'm older.
I recently tried to book tickets for
Rihanna and I booked tickets for
Ryanair. Um
I can Very good.
I've got something called Asperger's
syndrome, which means I'm a genius. Um
No, it's nice to be here. I've had a bit
of a rough week. I've actually moved
into a flat with with my boyfriend. Yes,
boyfriend, gay.
And uh and autistic, two ways I can't
think straight. And um
and I
[laughter]
Thank you. And um
That is a good one. So, I I usually when
I do clubs I swear a lot. So, I've got
to be PC. I've done a song which is
literally PC cuz it's about computers.
And I have done it three times and this
time people have laughed. So, if you
don't, you're wrong. Here we go.
Thank you. George Formby working in a
computer shop.
I work in the computer shop making
computer bright and clean. So much
crumbs and vomit and don't ask what's on
the screen. I do half the work charge
double the time, but you wouldn't want a
job like mine if you would find the
things I'd find when I'm cleaning
Microsoft Windows.
David Walliams wanted to update his
contact reminder. He brought me a
massive ring binder, but when I looked
all the contacts were from Grindr.
Cleaning Microsoft Windows.
Alesha Dixon's webcam was another case.
She said the picture was awful, but
actually it was just her face.
[cheering]
It was too lovely. Her face was too
lovely.
Here we go. Amanda Holden was the only
one whose Instagram was on the mark. She
said her outfits have so much spark. I
said I'm just jealous I'll never dress
like you cuz I don't shop in Primark.
And
I'm okay with that. CLEANING MICROSOFT
WINDOWS.
[applause]
SIMON COWELL'S Facebook was around the
bend. [music]
He brought it to me to try to mend. It
wasn't broken. He's just got no friends.
Cleaning Microsoft Windows.
[cheering]
[music]
[applause and cheering]
Oh,
Robert, I love you. Wow.
[cheering]
I mean, everything you said was
hilarious. You're [music] just a
beautiful soul. Comedy flows from you
like water. I love that you had a go at
us all. I think some people were more
hurt than others.
Some was just entirely truthful. Um
[laughter]
But
I just can't wait to see what you're
going to do next. Wow. [cheering]
From start to finish that was
hilariously funny. You're a shining
star. It's fantastic.
[cheering]
[applause and music]
You're very self-deprecating and I think
you have funny bones and [music]
your audition was fabulous.
Thank you. Very good.
[cheering]
[applause]
Well, Robert, you know what? You're very
unique, you're very quirky, very funny,
very naughty.
Robert,
which we like.
[cheering]
Thank you.
Maybe yes or no. IT'S A BIG FAT YES.
WOW.
[screaming]
I'M SAYING YES.
[music]
I'm saying yes.
Robert White,
you got four yeses. Congratulations.
[cheering]
[music]
A lovely man. Hello, everybody. Nice to
meet you and what's your name? My name
is Mr. Pants. Mr. Pants, I don't know
how to say it, but your fly's open and
something is poking out.
[laughter]
Is that your real name? Yes. Well, Mr.
Pants, Mr. Pants, can we get the Q-tip
for Simon over here? It's Mr. Pants.
Okay, Mr. Pants, tell me where you're
from. Brooklyn, New York.
[cheering]
What is your day job? Well, I used to go
to the office every day, but uh since
the pandemic, I've been virtually
replaced by sweatpants. Okay.
Okay.
You're a comedian? Sir, yes, sir. I'm
here to dazzle you with my stand-up
comedy routine.
So, what's the dream, Mr. Pants?
Vegas, baby.
[cheering]
Okay, I'm not going to ask any more
questions. Complete waste of time. Good
luck. Thank you.
Good [cheering] luck.
[applause]
[cheering]
Ladies and gentlemen,
[laughter]
MR. PANTS.
[cheering]
PLEASE, TERRY, MY father was Mr. Pants.
Look, I'm going to make this brief. I
only got one day left on my return
policy.
I inherited my father's jeans.
He immigrated here from a banana
republic.
It was very hard on me growing up. He
used to call me a huge waste.
You see, both of my parents wanted me to
become a lawyer.
Never even came close to becoming a
lawyer, but I was once involved in a
suit.
[applause]
But I've since traveled the world, went
to Spain, fell madly in love with a
Spanish sundress.
[laughter]
Then we broke up and I was pantaloons.
Yeah.
[applause]
I love him. But I'm happily married now.
Aw.
[laughter]
My wife and I are poly.
It's polyester.
[laughter]
Our daughter, Capri,
brought home a pair of sweatpants.
Hey, I want to be a supportive father,
but I want to see her date someone
ironed with a crease. This guy looked
like he'd been donated.
She asked if he could spend the night. I
said, "In my house, YOU'LL SLEEP IN
SEPARATE DRAWERS."
HEY GUYS, I'D LOVE TO TELL YOU MORE
JOKES, BUT UNFORTUNATELY, I left them in
my other pants.
Thank you so much. You've been a lovely
crowd of people.
I LIKE THAT. HE'S FUNNY.
FOR MR. PANTS.
I'M HAYDEN CRYSTAL. IT'S SO NICE TO meet
you.
Nice to meet you. Now, what are you
going to be doing here on AGT?
I'm going to be doing [music] stand-up
comedy. So, when did you decide you were
funny? We'll see what the feedback is
today. [laughter]
I was born deaf [music] into a family
that does not sign and they're all
hearing. So, it's just me.
So, communication has always been
something that I have struggled with. I
think early on I found that comedy is a
[music] language everyone understands.
If I say something and you laugh at it,
that's a connection.
I always love that feeling. Why [music]
AGT?
This is one of the biggest stages in the
world and watching some of the people
that AGT has been given opportunities to
has given me
more confidence to pursue this for
myself. [music]
America's Got Talent, it's my mom's
favorite show. We watch it together
growing up.
[music]
And it's
surreal to be here.
I'm like going to cry thinking about
that.
To be auditioning [music]
for America's Got Talent, that has been
the dream for me. All right, Hayden.
Who's the judge you want to impress the
most?
Honestly, I'm really hoping that Heidi
likes my dress. Oh, that's it. That's
it. I like it specifically, so we'll
see. All right. Go on out and make your
dream come true right now.
Thank you so much.
Oh, thank you. Go right on out.
[music]
[applause and cheering]
Hi.
Good evening.
How are you?
I'm totally kidding.
Not about the sign language, that part
is real. I'm working with an interpreter
tonight. I am really hard of hearing. I
perform my sets in English, but I do
like to start that way cuz it does make
heckling me an ADA violation.
Oh. Oh. Hello.
What's your name?
[applause]
How are you tonight?
Oh, I'm good. My name is Hayden Crystal.
I'm a comedian. Um I'm actually a
touring comic right now. But part of why
I wanted to come to America's Got Talent
is watching so many other comics with
disabilities come here and succeed
before I did, like Drew Lynch, um DJ
Demers years ago.
Uh
[cheering]
Yeah.
When I see other people with disability
on this stage and thriving, I know that
they were given the tools to be able to
succeed here, um which is No, yeah.
Thank you so much then for being here
tonight. We're ready for you.
Thank you. Okay. I'm going to start.
Um so I dual majored in college. Um I
studied sign language, uh and which that
felt like a freebie, right? Uh
But I also majored in zookeeping,
um which seemed like a really fun thing
at the time. Uh but now I have a degree
in American Sign Language and
zookeeping.
And um Koko, the sign language gorilla,
died like 4 years ago.
So what I'm saying is that comedy
has to work out for me. Uh
yeah, this has to go, guys. This has to
go good.
Uh
my safety net is dead. She's gone. So um
I know, it's very sad. So I actually um
I applied to work at the Koko Foundation
when I was in college, uh and they
rejected me because I have hearing loss.
But they
Yeah, boo boo, the Koko Foundation. Uh
They told me They told me I was a
liability issue because if the gorilla
were to sneak up on me, I would not be
able to hear it. Which I can't say with
any degree of certainty, uh
but probably that seems true. Um so you
guys seem like a nice crowd full of
hearing people, so I'm just going to
toss this question out to the room. Um
What are y'all going to do different if
a gorilla sneaks up on you?
Yeah, thank you. I would love to know.
Uh
[applause]
That makes a lot of sense. DM me after
the show. I am just desperate to know
what home field advantage y'all have uh
[laughter]
with your 2-second head start.
Ridiculous. Nothing. Nothing. The only
thing you're going to do different than
me is die scared. That's it.
That's the only thing. Yeah,
thank you.
[cheering]
Hayden, thank you so much for being here
tonight. I had a great time listening to
you. I love that you make fun of
yourself. I was laughing the whole time.
Uh Heidi, what did you think? We have
amazing comedians on the show, and I
think that you would be a great addition
to what we already have, so you can
really battle it OUT WITH THEM.
SIMON. UM WAS that a true story?
Yes. I mean, it's brilliantly funny.
Um
So seriously, and the fact you could
turn that into a funny story, which is
so crazy that they would do that. To
your point, what difference does it
make?
I You know I'm with you.
I've been trying to start Twitter beef
with them for like 10 years. So if you
become Listen, I'll join you.
[cheering]
I can also see
this means an awful lot to you. Yeah,
it's it's truly a privilege and an honor
to just be here. So thank you.
I'm really happy to have met
[cheering]
Thank you so much. I think we're going
to vote now for you. Heidi, what what is
your vote? I want to see you more, so
I'm going to give you a first yes.
[cheering]
I'm going to give you your second yes.
[music]
Simon. Hayden, I'm saying yes to you,
and Julie, I want to say yes to you.
[cheering and music]
Good luck, Hayden.
I think Howie would have loved it.
Hayden,
talk You seem very emotional. Talk to me
right now. What are you feeling?
Just
validation from some place that really
meant a lot to me in starting this, and
to be here it's unbelievable. And then I
felt like I already won just making it
to tonight, and that was
It couldn't have been
[music]